(Hwang In Youp)
(Lee Hye Ri)
(Baek Sung Chul, Lee Yul Eum)
(Dream To You)
(All people, events, and backgrounds are fictional.)
(This drama includes footage created using AI.)
(Children and animals were filmed under strict safety guidelines.)
(Episode 7)
(Jaejae Noodles)
- Going for a run? - Yes.
Why are you running this late at night?
So I don't run into him.
You mean Su Bin?
That's why you've been working from home lately?
See? I told you I was right, didn't I? I was right.
A man's heart, right?
I told you it takes a man to know one.
You're right.
You're asking for it. Darn you.
I got killed!
Sending the revised draft.
(Gyeongseong Love Song Screenplay Revised Draft)
Finally, a chance to see her.
I guess I still haven't gotten over her.
Mister.
- Focus. - Okay, okay. Here.
Okay.
Here, let me peel it for you.
- Okay. - Thank you.
You're welcome.
- I got it out. - You did?
I really miss her.
Who?
- A coworker. - A coworker?
- A friend. - I know.
I only asked because it's weird to miss a coworker.
Why is it weird?
They say that missing someone is the same as loving them.
And it's hard to love a coworker.
You're really smart.
- Do you take after your mom? - Yes. I got my mom's brains,
and they say I have my dad's looks.
- I can see that. - Kim Sung Chan, Daddy's here.
Dad.
- Dad. - Come here.
There you go.
- Did you have fun with him? - Yes.
Oh, my goodness.
Sorry.
A large group showed up at your mom's shop.
- It's okay. I was here for a bit. - I'll buy you a drink next time.
- You don't need to. - Okay, say goodbye, "Seung Chan."
- Okay. Bye, "Seung Chan." - "Seung Chan"?
Right. "Seung Chan." See you next time.
(Kim Sung Chan)
Let's go, let's go. Come on, this way. There we go.
- Go on. - Okay, we're going.
- Bye. - Bye.
Oh my, you're so cute. Let's go, let's go.
He's a good dad.
Grandma, Mom.
- I brought some twisted donuts. - I'm eating some right now.
- What? - Yi Jae was just here.
Why aren't you two hanging out these days?
We're working separately.
So, what are you two doing?
I'm studying for the driver's permit test,
and she's learning to read and write.
You're getting your license?
I need to be able to go far away by myself now.
You can go with me.
And I can teach you how to drive.
They say you should never learn how to drive from family.
Forget it. Look.
I still don't know it all, but I've definitely memorized this.
You wrote Mom and my names?
You'll be writing poems soon.
But...
Like this. And this.
Hey, isn't that a 'bieup'? I know that one!
It's 'Bin.'
You haven't made a single mistake.
Are you nervous because Su Bin is here?
- Oh, honestly. - Bin.
Bin. There, right?
Driver Kim.
What are you doing waiting out here in the open like this?
Your mother is here, isn't she?
Your father told me to bring her.
If he wants to see her that badly, tell him to come himself.
Su Bin.
If you come here again, I will call the police.
All right, the cast is all here. Now, let's get the video on screen.
Let's have the Catfish Man enter.
(The 7th Chain-Mate enters.)
Hello.
I brought this.
- Please, have a seat anywhere. - Have a seat.
All right.
Yes. Where?
The wide shot is good.
- Camera 3 and 4. - Sa Rang.
- Please move to the left.. - this is absolutely huge.
The moment the Catfish Man walked in, the whole vibe changed.
This is a massive hit.
Yes, this is good. Let's get a group shot of the men...
and capture all their reactions.
They're reacting well to the Catfish Man.
Yes, that's good.
We're getting good audio pickup, right?
I've looked forward to meeting you all.
Okay, production team, double-check...
the next interview and the outdoor set.
Yes, that's good.
We have some bread, grapes and egg tarts.
Sir.
Yu Geon is only acting this way because he feels sorry.
And you're only doing it because you care about him.
And Yu Geon is so stubborn, you know.
He could just ask my sister and Su Bin to cast him.
I wonder who he takes after to be so stubborn.
He takes after me.
I was the same way.
What good is all that pride?
I couldn't even ask anyone for a favour.
Sir.
- Hello. - Su Bin. It's been a while.
Well...
Is Yi Jae with you?
No. I'm by myself today.
I see.
- Would you like to come in? - Oh, no. It's okay.
Well, it's nothing much,
but I'd like Yi Jae...
to take a look at this for me.
What is this?
Don't feel pressured at all. All right?
I'm leaving now.
- Wait, sir, this... - Go on inside.
(Yu Geon's Dream, Bus 31 - As Mail Carrier)
(Letter Of The Day - As Post Office Employee 3)
(Low Voice - As Call Center Agent)
(Late Arrival - As Flight Attendant)
(Going To School - As Student 3)
Sim Yu Geon. He's really worked hard.
(Sending the revised version.)
He's seen it but hasn't replied.
(Woo Su Bin)
What's this?
Wait, no.
That makes it look like I've been waiting.
But I have been waiting, haven't I?
I was waiting for feedback.
Hello.
What? Now?
To the studio?
Oh my goodness, now?
Well... I need some time to get there.
Okay. See you later.
That was very natural.
See?
So much for being colleagues.
Oh, I was wondering who that was.
- You could've just come in. - It's called being polite.
Okay.
You're my...
Well...
- Can I come over here? - Sure.
Time for Plan B.
(Ten Reasons Why A Contract Marriage Is Dangerous)
It has everything he starred, even the most recent shows.
Did Mr. Sim give this to you?
- It's a little over an hour long. - What? Has it been an hour already?
Time flew by so fast.
I know, right? The time I waited for you felt longer...
What?
Well...
It's probably because Yu Geon is such a good actor.
Yes, that's exactly what I was going to say.
So, is there a role Yu Geon could play...
A small role...
Right, even a small role would be nice.
- No, I don't want that. - What?
I hate when it feels like a handout.
It wouldn't be fair to Yu Geon.
Let's have him audition.
But he won't want to audition if I'm the one who asks.
If he gets the part, it'll be awkward,
and if he doesn't, his feelings will get hurt.
Then it would be better to go through his agency.
He doesn't have an agency.
What? So he's been doing it all by himself?
I mean, the difference between having an agency and not is huge.
The audition opportunities themselves are completely different.
Oh my goodness. I just don't understand him.
Seriously, actors with his looks and talent...
aren't a dime a dozen, you know.
I just don't get it.
What?
You know, you've always had a thing for his looks.
- To the point of making me jealous. - I was the one who was jealous.
You said it yourself. That a face like Sim Yu Geon's...
is made for the camera.
When did I say that? I filmed your face way more.
What?
- Well... - That might be true.
We were dating...
Well, that's all in the past.
Besides, I can't resist pretty things...
What?
Well, I should get going.
- Where are you going? - Why? What?
We need to have a meeting about the revised script.
Right.
Should we do it here or there?
Here?
(Name: Sim Yu Geon)
Why would you agree to a contract like this?
I don't see what I have to lose.
You've already lost the most important thing.
Because I'm the one who bought your heart.
You must never fall in love with Ha Na.
- But I don't have those feelings. - Of course you don't. I took them.
And you'd better not have them in the future.
Isn't it amusing?
That this little scrap of paper has your body and soul all tied up.
Wow.
Amazing. I love people like you.
An investment in you shows immediate returns.
It makes spending money satisfying.
Get in.
No. You're sitting next to me. Here.
Okay.
Is someone else joining us?
- Hi. - Oh, you're here already.
Sim Yu Geon.
Su Bin.
Do you two know each other?
Perfect.
I'll be able to make it to the gym before it closes.
You must be happy to see him here.
- Right, Director Ian? - What do you think you're doing?
What do you mean, what am I doing?
I'm saying we should cast this young man as Mu Gyeom.
What?
You've really gotten more audacious over the years.
First, you came up with an unscheduled audition,
and now you're just casting roles yourself.
The lead role, at that.
Director Ian, stop blocking the door and have a seat so we can talk.
You sit down too.
Sim Yu Geon. Come out here.
Get out here now.
I guess I won't make it to the gym.
What are you doing here?
Yi Jae was so careful about even suggesting you audition.
I guess we were worried for nothing.
You should've just asked me or Yi Jae for help.
It would have been much easier.
Rather than burdening the people I care about,
- this is easier for me. - So you create a mess like this?
I didn't expect to see you here.
I'm sorry.
If you were going to use your connections all along,
you should've done it when you were still young and naive.
After all the hardships you went through...
Why now?
What do you know about it?
You have no idea how I've managed to survive until now,
so why do you say that?
I should've done it when I was young and naive?
Back then, I did the best I possibly could,
and right now, this is the best I can do.
Fine.
But take a good look in the mirror.
Is that the face of someone who's doing their best?
Sim Yu Geon.
I never particularly liked you,
but I have to admit, there was something admirable about you.
But...
not anymore.
Ian.
Hey.
Hey, you.
Are you just going to walk out?
First, just calm down.
- Just listen to me. - You crossed the line too.
Just like the audition of Oh Ha Na, you should have at least...
had the decency to sneak around behind my back.
I thought he was going to audition.
And that he's a friend of yours? So isn't this a good thing?
Exactly. That means you're the one who stole his opportunity.
If it weren't for this deal, he could've landed any part...
You have to give one thing up to get another.
You have to protect Joo Yi Jae.
Why are you bringing up Joo Yi Jae now?
What we have to do in this situation is...
accept Sim Yu Geon,
and protect Joo Yi Jae. That's it.
- Hey. - Snap out of it.
No matter what great awards you've won...
or how spectacular your debut was, this is only your second film.
A romance that's hard to get funding for?
On top of that, a period drama?
And you're co-directing with an unproven rookie. Hey!
You're doing everything you want to do right now.
Can't you give up that one thing?
If it weren't for CEO Ahn,
it wouldn't have been easy for us to get this far.
Let's remember our place.
You're right.
"We're not in a position to do something like this."
You should have told me from the start, sir.
You said you had to do this no matter what.
So what was I supposed to do? You said it was your dream.
When you were just 22,
you were wandering around without a home...
and came to me with just that one script.
I still remember that day vividly.
Just like you're trying to keep your promise to Joo Yi Jae,
I'm also...
just trying to keep my promise to you.
But since I lack the ability, this was the best I could do.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ian.
Come on in, everyone. The food's getting cold.
Director Woo.
You heard from CEO Seo, right?
Cast Sim Yu Geon.
Or are you going to drop Joo Yi Jae?
You're going to push for Sim Yu Geon no matter what,
and I'm going to protect Joo Yi Jae no matter what.
It seems like we already have our conclusion.
I like that you're quick.
I need to make things clear right here and now.
Our movie...
won't fall through just because we lose you,
but it can't be made without Director Joo Yi Jae.
You decided to invest after reading Director Joo's script,
I'd appreciate it if you didn't tell us...
to give up on her.
I only gave it the time of day because it was your second project.
Otherwise,
do you think the script would have even made it to my desk?
Anyway, I got the answer I wanted, so I'll be going now.
You're leaving already?
I have to go boxing.
Even if I leave now, I'll only get an hour in.
What are you doing? Get up.
Take care.
By the way.
You're looking for a top star for the female lead, right?
Since I saved you the time you would have spent looking for a male lead,
spend that time on the female lead and make it a great film.
- This rice wine... - I can't.
You're really putting it away, aren't you?
Who said they were having this earlier?
- It was you. - No, it wasn't me.
In Wook, coming back from work?
- Yes. - Aren't you dying to know his job?
- I know, right? - Right.
Hurry and get changed. We were just about to play Truth or Dare.
I am a little tired. You all have fun.
Right. It is understandable that he is tired.
- That's a shame. - I know.
(Love Chain)
The two of them are going out to the terrace. Follow them.
Is something wrong?
You look troubled.
Do not tell Yi Jae what we talked about earlier.
Yu Geon, you are here.
What is going on? Why do you look so handsome today?
Did you play a handsome character?
Why are you here?
Well, you were not answering,
and your motorcycle was parked out front of your home,
so I thought you were home and came up.
But is something wrong?
You look a little down today.
I asked why you came.
Right.
Give me your hand.
Hurry up.
(Oh Ha Na)
Ta-da. I stole it from Mom's drawer.
Now my real journey can finally begin.
I did good, right?
Showing up unannounced like this...
is uncomfortable and unpleasant.
Are you mad? Because I came without notice?
I am sorry.
- From now on... - And we should stop being friends.
How can we be friends?
Friendship is for people who are alike.
Then...
until now, what were we?
Oh Ha Na and...
Extra One.
Leave.
(Expiration Date: 10,000 Years)
Oh my gosh, my stick figure storyboard turned into this quality?
- Who is the storyboard artist? - Director Ian did it.
Su Bin... I mean...
Director Woo creates storyboards himself?
Yes, he does not have a storyboard artist.
He usually does them himself.
No wonder. It is as if he took it straight from my mind.
- You are here. - Jennie, can you give us a moment?
Yes.
- Why? - We're discussing it today,
but I thought it would be best if you knew beforehand.
What is it?
The role of Mu Gyeom.
Sim Yu Geon got it. It is confirmed.
Yu Geon? The Sim Yu Geon that I know?
Wait, how?
I thought he was supposed to audition. Has he done it already?
I heard Yu Geon is with Top Line Entertainment.
As you know,
CEO Ahn Soo Hee is our company's business partner.
Sim Yu Geon is with that agency?
He seems to be a hot prospect.
Especially since a powerful agency is backing him.
What is with Sim Yu Geon? I feel so pleasantly betrayed.
You seem really happy about it.
Of course I am happy. But really, this is amazing.
I guess if it is meant to be, it will be.
If you are happy,
then that is all that matters.
I am sorry.
I was only thinking about myself. Are you okay?
We were going to have Yu Geon audition anyway.
I am happy about it too.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
- Keep up the good work. - Good work today.
- Good work. - You too.
Good work.
Hey, Sim Yu Geon.
Hey, why the long face? We should be celebrating.
- I'm sorry. - Sorry for what?
I'm grateful that you're going to be Mu Gyeom.
I know how much this movie means to you,
and I know I shouldn't be like this.
Yu Geon.
That's just how life is sometimes. Sometimes, a meteorite...
just crashes down right in front of you.
It's not your land, so you wonder if it's really yours, right?
But if you pick it up, it's yours.
You seized this opportunity. So don't be timid.
Our Mu Gyeom isn't like that.
- Yi Jae, but... - I'm not trying to comfort you.
I'm saying this...
because you might think CEO Ahn helped you get cast.
Do you think Woo Su Bin and I are pushovers?
Do we seem like people who'd say yes to something we hate?
It's not that, but...
Hey, what is really wrong with you?
Do you need a little smack to come to your senses?
Yi Jae.
There's no way I can hide this...
and still be in your movie. It just doesn't feel right.
The door is opening.
Su Bin told me not to say anything.
Actually, CEO Ahn made a demand.
If they didn't cast me the lead,
she said she'd have you removed as the director.
Su Bin cast me to protect you.
Hey, Director Woo.
I thought you went home.
I brought some kimbap for a late-night snack.
I was getting hungry. Thanks.
So did you...
- go see Yu Geon? - Yes.
He was so down in the dumps, so I gave him a good talking-to.
He's talented.
- He'll do fine. - Yes.
Thanks for the food.
Thank you.
This looks delicious.
(Yu Geon's Dream)
(Bus 31 - As Mail Carrier)
(Letter Of The Day - As Post Office Employee 3)
I heard your father gave this to Su Bin.
To ask him to take care of you.
If you were going to use your connections all along,
you should've done it when you were still young and naive.
After all the hardships you went through...
Why now?
You've already lost the most important thing.
Because I'm the one who bought your heart.
You must never fall in love with Ha Na.
Ta-da. I stole it from Mom's drawer.
Now my real journey can finally begin.
I did good, right?
(Expiration Date: 10,000 Years)
(Simsim Seafood)
(Actor Sim Yu Geon)
Yes? Is something wrong?
Dad.
I'm speaking. What's wrong?
I got cast.
I'm the lead in a movie.
Really?
Then why do you sound like that?
Because I'm happy.
Is that so?
All right. You've worked hard.
Bye.
Dad.
Thank you.
Are you really sure it's okay to stay at my house?
If you ask me one more time, that'll be the tenth time.
Stop asking. I'm telling you, I'm really fine.
It's just, you're such an important person and this place is so shabby.
When I worked abroad, I slept in worse places.
I can even sleep outdoors as long as I have a sleeping bag.
I'll put your luggage away.
Where are you going?
The New York shoot is next week.
You know my schedule for next week,
but I guess you didn't know my contract ended last week?
Since when have we ever been sticklers for dates?
I'm going independent.
- I'm not renewing my contract. - You're going to retire?
No. Why would you think I'd quit this line of work?
Because you've never wanted to do it.
I probably never had a moment to think...
about whether I wanted to or not.
From now on,
I'm going to live my life for myself.
- Chae Yeon, is the luggage loaded? - Yes.
Thank you for everything up to now, ma'am.
Is it because of Sim Yu Geon?
The way you're acting like a petulant teenager,
isn't it because of him?
Honestly, even if you have no one to turn to,
how could you fall for a guy like that?
- You'd be better getting therapy. - Mom.
- What? - It's because of you, Mom.
You make me feel like I'm suffocating.
You were already digging into Sim Yu Geon's background?
Good grief, listen to her. What do you take your mother for?
You think I only looked into his past?
I've also considered what he can do in the future.
So don't mess with me.
Just go clear your head for a day or two and come back.
Gangneung should do the trick.
Chae Yeon, use the company card. And don't just feed Ha Na sweets.
Yes.
Director Kang, release an article...
that Ha Na is halting all activities.
The reason? Just make something up.
Ha Na, do you really have to go this far?
Look. It's Jaden.
Who's that? Should I go up to him?
No, pass on him.
I heard he's a CEO now.
You can't trust people who are CEOs. Like my mom.
Okay, pass on the CEO.
Look. It's Director Ian.
Should I get him? Should I go now?
No.
We can't approach him.
But he's the director of Gyeongseong Love Song.
Who else are you going to ask for the script?
- Her. - What?
Ha Na, wait!
Director Joo Yi Jae.
Oh Ha Na?
But how do you know me?
I was a huge fan of "Yi Jae Will Be There."
And we also met at the department store event, right?
Wouldn't you call this fate?
- Fate? - Yes.
So, what was it you wanted to talk to me about?
Please give me the script for Gyeongseong Love Song.
I thought CEO Ahn has it.
Exactly. I should have stolen it.
Excuse me?
I really want to do that project, Director.
I'm desperate. I've never felt this way before.
- Really? - Yes.
Can you hear it?
Nan Yeong breathing and living inside of me.
Yes, I can. I'll give it to you. How should I get it to you?
- Should I give it to your manager? - No.
Could I get your number, sis?
"Sis"?
It's flattering. Did Oh Ha Na just ask for my number?
But in return, what happened today...
is our little secret.
- Okay. - Shhh.
(Ahn Yoo Jung)
(Im Min Joo)
Of course, top actors are booked solid...
for their next few projects.
So at least there's a chance with actress Yoon Min Joo...
- if we adjust the filming dates. - What about Oh Ha Na?
Well...
She's in talks for another project right now.
No, there was an article a few days ago...
saying she's taking a hiatus.
Really?
- Did I miss it? - I'm here.
(Action.)
Action.
- What's going on? - You can't just come in here.
- Is that a gun? - Excuse me.
- Come on, we're in a meeting... - Comrades.
- Nan Yeong? - Did she come dressed like that?
This is no time to be standing around.
If we just sit around discussing the current state of affairs,
nothing will change.
Do you know how I felt when I blew up Wolhwajeong and left?
I have no place to return to now. I can only move forward.
Sadness is fleeting,
but joy is eternal.
That's right, comrade Nan Yeong.
Let's march toward independence together.
Why did you only appear now?
Just as you said,
it was like Nan Yeong is alive and breathing.
Director Joo Yi Jae?
Director.
I've also prepared for Scene 34. Shall I perform it right now?
Oh Ha Na, what do you think you're doing right now?
I am confident that I can do a great job as Nan Yeong.
- Give me the part. I'm begging you. - Yes.
You were good.
It was the same Oh Ha Na acting I've always seen.
What I'm saying is, it wasn't special.
Then may I tell you the special reason...
why you should cast me?
I'm curious.
I...
know someone who has lived a life just like Nan Yeong's.
A child who, since she was young, had no dream of her own...
and only lived as she was told.
Not even knowing that her world was a small prison.
Then she met someone like Mu Gyeom and realised.
Okay, you shoot the next take.
If I break out of my world,
there might be a bigger world out there.
I want to live...
in the same world as that person.
So she blew up her entire world and ran out.
I'm...
no longer with Top Line Entertainment.
I don't have an agency right now.
And I plan to keep taking on challenges by myself from now on.
I also requested this script from Director Joo Yi Jae myself.
Wait, then does CEO Ahn Soo Hee know about this situation?
She has no idea.
So if...
I become Nan Yeong,
I think I'll have to hide it as much as possible...
until filming starts.
I'm sorry.
Please help me.
Help me live as Oh Ha Na,
and no longer as Ahn Soo Hee's daughter.
If the first step of my independence is to become Nan Yeong,
I think it will give me great strength.
Nan Yeong's independence,
after all, has a happy ending.
Could you please wait outside for a moment?
Sorry for the wait. Have a seat.
Oh Ha Na.
Let's work together.
I hope you can bring Nan Yeong's character to life.
Thank you.
I promise I will...
do my absolute best to become the best Nan Yeong I can be.
Do you know...
why I didn't cast you back then?
You rejected me because my English wasn't good enough.
The deciding factor was your attitude.
You were like an elementary schooler,
dragged here by your mom against your will.
There's no fooling a director's eye, is there?
But what I saw today was different.
You were impressive, and now I have high hopes.
Thank you.
Anyway, as for the schedule going forward,
it will be sent directly to you.
Confidentiality is key.
And don't mention it to your co-star, either.
Oh, right. Mu Gyeom.
Is it an actor I know?
Who is it?
- I told you not to come... - Why?
Why did you do that?
Why did you sign a contract with my mom?
Because I have to become somebody.
So, please.
Just please, stay away from me.
That contract...
I signed it on the condition...
that I would never fall in love with you.
You're lying.
No, I mean...
What kind of contract is that?
Yu Geon...
Did you ever love me?
No.
Then why?
What was there between us, then?
I wonder.
What was there between us?
For me, there was definitely nothing.
You're right.
Birds of a feather flock together.
I was wrong about you.
(Mu Gyeom, Practice, Studying Japanese, Pronunciation)
(Not too drunk, Not a drunkard, Just a slight stagger)
(Deliver lines with a slight smile.)
(When looking at Nan Yeong, pause a beat before reacting.)
(Move smoothly. No shaky hands.)
Yes, Dad.
I'm here.
You're here.
Why are you here alone? Where's Joo Yeong Jae?
I sent him to the market on an errand.
Here.
- What is it? - Go make this delivery first.
I put the address on it.
"3784..."
Delivery.
- Su Bin! - Yes.
Come in.
Why are you here?
I asked your father to send you.
You did?
(CEO Seo In Wook, Actor Oh Ha Na)
- It's a pleasure to work with you. - Me too.
You're here?
You're here.
Do you two know each other?
We used to.
In the past.
- From "Contract Marriage"? - I was the lead and he was Extra 1.
Right?
- What's going on? - We're here for a table read.
Say hi. That's Nan Yeong, and this is Mu Gyeom.
- What? - But has Mu Gyeom signed on yet?
I wonder if my Mom signed it for him.
Good question. Did he?
That didn't sound like a question.
"Scene 47. A street. Night. In the middle of all the commotion,"
"Nan Yeong and Mu Gyeom in western attire walk side by side."
"Despite the noise around them, the two walk slowly."
"From every angle, you don't seem to have a care in the world."
"What do you think?"
"Not beneath the lanterns of Wolhwajeong,"
"but I'm here, illuminated by this moonlight."
"I look pretty charming, don't I?"
"Why must you always turn everything into a joke?"
Go, Gyeongseong Love Song.
You two are so awkward.
You're supposed to be in love soon. Why don't you try to get along?
I'd love to.
But I'm not sure if Yu Geon can.
He may seem gruff, but he's a great guy on the inside.
Is that so?
I guess you're the type who's completely different on the inside.
Your acting isn't bad,
but you two don't seem to make any eye contact.
Even if it's just a table read,
you need to look at each other and match your pacing.
If you're just going to read separately,
you might as well have done it at home.
- I'm sorry. - Sorry.
But I actually found it amazing.
How can you have such natural back-and-forth...
without even looking at each other?
Maybe they had a falling-out.
Looks like I was right.
They have to be friends first to fall out.
I've seen them together.
- They looked pretty close. - Really?
If the friendship is over,
maybe you should try falling in love.
You're supposed to have a romance,
but a broken friendship isn't right for that, is it?
I'm sure they'll be different once the cameras roll.
But falling in love will be even harder.
Why don't you say something?
Can you love me?
I have to. The directors told me to.
Aren't you, Ha Na?
If it helps the show, I'm prepared to do anything.
That's disappointing.
Because I'm already in love.
There's definitely something between them.
- I'm dying to know, aren't you? - Not really.
Hey, I'm telling you, I've never seen that look...
on Sim Yu Geon's face before.
It was like a cold, yet sad look in his eyes?
Sounds more like a breakup than a falling-out.
Perfect. That means they've already been in love.
- Really? - We'll get great emotional depth.
Should we shoot the breakup scene first?
What you just said was really uncalled for.
I'm saying, you don't need to worry about it so much.
They can't hide their feelings on set either. It'll all come out.
We just need to catch those moments and draw their emotions out.
In that case, a love that's more like a war...
would be even better.
I also prefer that to a quiet romance.
I write much better when my boyfriend and I...
were at each other's throats.
I wonder if it's because the emotional waves are bigger.
- When? - What?
Well, doesn't everyone date someone on campus in college?
I haven't.
Really?
Hey, that's something you can only do at that age.
What were you doing instead?
I was busy carrying equipment on set...
and bought one baguette to make it last the whole week.
Okay, forget it. Let's move on.
Was that really love, at that age?
Then what about us back then?
When we were 18 and 19.
What was that then?
It was love.
Back when we were 18 and 19.
And even now.
I think it's love.
I know...
that you cast Yu Geon to protect me.
- Yi Jae. - I'm not trying to blame you.
I don't blame you anymore.
It's just...
what that feeling must be like...
I've been thinking about it for a while.
All great things start from something small, right?
Just from you liking me,
you came to love movies.
But...
the truly great thing...
is that feeling, isn't it?
And the feeling...
you decided to hold back.
Your feelings are so big...
that I can't pretend I don't see them, Woo Su Bin.
So...
don't hold back.
I'm already so nervous, what am I going to do?
Even the masters...
probably get nervous the day before their first shoot.
- You think so? - So I come the day before...
- Yes. - and in my head...
- I run a simulation. - How?
Here, look.
The art department will be the first to arrive.
- Okay. - They'll double-check the signs...
and set up that steamy soup restaurant to look just right.
- The cinematographer over there... - Yes?
He'll be eating gummies, waiting for the setup to be done.
Yes, Assistant Director. I'm on my way now.
Always watch your step on set.
Tripping over a cable is a huge deal.
- Okay. - Watch out for lighting equipment.
Yi Jae.
And this here...
is your seat, Director Joo Yi Jae.
(Director Joo Yi Jae)
Sit here, and with everything you've got,
call, "Ready."
"Action."
- Me? - Yes.
(Director Woo Su Bin, Director Joo Yi Jae)
Everyone...
will be waiting for your cue.
Go ahead.
Ready.
Action.
(Dream To You)
Directors, If you witness...
any romantic behaviour between the staff members,
please report it to me immediately.
You need to stick right by my side and show my mom.
Show her that there's absolutely no love between us.
Relax.
Oh Ha Na. Everyone, wrap it up.
I'll drop out, CEO Ahn.
This all happened because of your pathetic act of defiance.
I'm sorry. This is my fault.
I regret ever fixing you.
I guess once something is broken,
it's hard to be whole again.
Yi Jae.